<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<works>
	<work>
		<title>Piccsy</title>
		<image_path>images/work/piccsy/</image_path>
		<description><![CDATA[
			Piccsy is an image discovery network for creative professionals. We launched the site in late 2010 and quickly grew to attracting over three and a half million visitors per month. 

			Piccsy has been through three iterations, shown sequentially here -- with the latest & current version displayed first.
		]]></description>
		<keywords>// Product Development // Creative Direction // Marketing</keywords>
		<link>http://www.piccsy.com</link>
	</work>
	<work>
		<title>Piccsy Playground</title>
		<image_path>images/work/piccsy-playground/</image_path>
		<description><![CDATA[
			Piccsy Playground is a series of labs projects we created to experiment with product development, design, and web technologies, while simultaneously promoting Piccsy to creative professionals.

Selected works are shown here, with the Piccsy Pitchdeck & Recite (also Playground projects) displayed below.
		]]></description>
		<keywords>// Creative Direction // Marketing</keywords>
		<link>http://www.piccsy.com/everything-design</link>
	</work>
	<work>
		<title>Piccsy Pitchdeck</title>
		<image_path>images/work/piccsy-pitchdeck/</image_path>
		<description><![CDATA[
			After deciding to seek investment in the summer of 2012, we created an interactive & animated pitch-deck for Piccsy.

The deck got significant online attention--most notably from Techcrunch who announced "Death to Powerpoint! Piccsy Rethinks the Pitchdeck"--and resulted in over 50 meetings with the top venture capitalists in North America.
		]]></description>
		<keywords>// Creative Direction // Marketing</keywords>
		<link>http://www.piccsy.com/investors</link>
	</work>
	<work>
		<title>Recite</title>
		<image_path>images/work/recite/</image_path>
		<description><![CDATA[
			Realizing a trend in the proliferation of "visual quotes" on Piccsy and throughout the web, we quickly responded by creating Recite -- a web product that includes over 50 beautiful & dynamic typographic templates enabling users to "turn a quote into a masterpiece" in seconds.
		]]></description>
		<keywords>// Product Development // Creative Direction // Marketing</keywords>
		<link>http://www.recitethis.com</link>
	</work>
	<work>
		<title>Rememberum</title>
		<image_path>images/work/rememberum/</image_path>
		<description><![CDATA[
			Rememberum empowers people to seamlessly create beautiful, permanent online memorials to celebrate their loved ones. Memorials are shared with friends and family, who can in-turn share memories, photos, and videos to help create a lasting legacy that can be updated at any time.

We launched the produce with a microsite tribute to Steve Jobs, designed in the classic Mac OS GUI. 
		]]></description>
		<keywords>// Product Development // Creative Direction // Marketing</keywords>
		<link>http://www.rememberum.com</link>
	</work>
	<work>
		<title>EveryGuyed</title>
		<image_path>images/work/everyguyed/</image_path>
		<description><![CDATA[
			EveryGuyed is a men's lifestyle network consisting of over 10 blogs, primarily in the mens fashion category. We sold the site in 2011, after growing it to over five million visitors per year.

In addition to the websites & promotional materials, we also produced a t-shirt collection, plush toy mascot, and event series.
		]]></description>
		<keywords>// Brand Development // Editorial Direction // Creative Direction </keywords>
		<link>http://www.everyguyed.com</link>
	</work>
	<work>
		<title>Revolver</title>
		<image_path>images/work/revolver/</image_path>
		<description><![CDATA[
			Revolver is a men's lifestyle website, curating the best videos from across the web for men with discerning taste in culture. 
		]]></description>
		<keywords>// Brand Development // Editorial Direction // Creative Direction</keywords>
		<link>http://www.gorevolver.com</link>
	</work>
	<work>
		<title>Moxy Creative</title>
		<image_path>images/work/moxy-creative/</image_path>
		<description><![CDATA[
			Moxy Creative is a boutique design firm, and previously the in-house creative agency of EveryGuyed. 

While managing EveryGuyed, we developed a variety of promotional print series targeting creative-oriented men, which resulted in significant press from outlets including: Computer Arts, GQ, MTV, Spike, Vanity Fair, and Vibe.
		]]></description>
		<keywords>// Brand Development // Creative Direction // Marketing</keywords>
		<link>http://www.moxycreative.com</link>
	</work>
	<work>
		<title>JR Mint</title>
		<image_path>images/work/jr-mint/</image_path>
		<description><![CDATA[
			JR Mint needed a unique way to release an album, so we conceptualized an interactive microsite that highlights individual songs & lyrics with icon-based illustrations.

Also shown here are promotional materials and album+mixtape covers.
		]]></description>
		<keywords>// Brand Development // Creative Direction // Marketing</keywords>
		<link>http://www.planetminty.com/goldenticket</link>
	</work>
	<work>
		<title>Vizualize.Me</title>
		<image_path>images/work/visualize-me/</image_path>
		<description><![CDATA[
			Vizualize.Me enables users to visualize their LinkedIn resume in an beautiful infographic within seconds. 

Winner of Start Up Weekend Toronto 2011.
		]]></description>
		<keywords>// Brand Development // Creative Direction // Marketing</keywords>
		<link>http://www.vizualize.me</link>
	</work>
	<work>
		<title>Torso: T-Shirt Graphics Exposed</title>
		<image_path>images/work/torso/</image_path>
		<description><![CDATA[
			Torso is a coffee table booked--published by Gestalten--that features the world's most interesting graphic t-shirts.

Available for purchase on Amazon.
		]]></description>
		<keywords>// Editorial Direction // Creative Direction</keywords>
		<link>http://www.amazon.com/Torso-Streetwear-T-Shirt-Graphics-Exposed</link>
	</work>
</works>